(Sheldon:)I've got to find a way
to stop this thing.
(Leonard:)Buddy, I don't think you can. I mean,
once its out there, it's out there.
(Leonard:)This thing is like the science
equivalent of a sex tape.
(Sheldon:)Frankly, I'd prefer a sex tape.
(Leonard:)You don't know
what a sex tape is, do you?
(Penny:)No.
(Howard:)Make sure you guys get
to the restaurant by 8:00.
(Howard:)Bernadette's
meeting me there at 8:30.
(Howard:)-I don't want to blow the surprise.
-We'll be there.
Got it. Now, I have
a question about the song.
(Raj:)I was thinking at some point
I could bust out a little rap.
Nah, nah, nuh, nuh, nuh, no.
(Raj:)Come on, come on,
you haven't even heard it yet.
(Raj:)Leonard, give me a beat.
(Leonard:)I will not.
(Raj:)Please?
(Howard:)-No, I want this to be romantic.
-it will be!
(Raj:)I don't call anyone a ho,
and the only time
I use the phrase "my bitch,"
I'm referring to you.
There he is!